乔伊
Joey?
我的天啊
Oh,my God.
好吧
Okay.
那么
So..
我想  我们该正式一点  对吧
I guess we should make it official,huh?
听着  瑞秋  我
Look,Rach,I..
嘿  罗斯来了
Hey,Ross is here!
嘿  瞧我的好朋友罗斯来了
Hey,look,it's my good friend Ross!
嘿  罗斯  嘿  乔伊
Hey,Ross.  Hey,Joey.
嘿  你好 嘿  你好
Hey,you.  Hey,you.
他还送花呢
And he brought flowers!
谢了  罗斯
Thanks,Ross.
我倒是那种喜欢送糖果的人
I'm really more of a candy kind of guy.
你今天真诡异
You're weird today.
听着  我有事想跟你谈
Listen,I wanted to talk to you about something.
事实上  我也需要跟你谈谈
Yeah. Actually,I kind of need to talk to you too.
乔伊  你可以回避一下吗 不行
Joey,could you give us a minute?  No.
什么  我很抱歉  我是说做不到
What?  I'm sorry. I meant,"No."
嘿  瞧瞧谁来了
Hi. Hey,look who's here.
我的孙女在哪
Where's my granddaughter?
我一直在练习变魔术
I've been practicing my magic tricks.
他从我耳后变出一个硬币
He pulled a quarter out of my ear.
嘿  妈呢  她去接莉蒂阿姨
Hey,where's Mom?  She went to pick up Aunt Liddy.
莉蒂阿姨要来
Aunt Liddy's coming?
那我们又可以得到5块零花钱啦
That means we get $5 each!
我何时才可以见到艾玛
So when do I get to meet Emma
然后表演这个给她看
and show her this:
好耶  哇
Okay,wow.
艾玛在育婴室
Emma's in the nursery.
如果你要看她  我现在就带你去
I'll take you now if you want.
但是我真的想要跟你谈谈
But I really want to talk to you.
我知道  我也要跟你谈谈
I know. I still need to talk to you.
但是在你们谈之前  我需要跟你谈谈
But before you guys do that,I need to talk to you.
还有罗斯  我也要跟你谈谈
And Ross,I need to talk to you.
那我需要跟你谈谈 谈什么
And I need to talk to you.  About what?
看你知不知道他们是要谈什么
To see if you know what these guys are talking about.
《老友记》  第九季 第1集   无人求婚
Friends S09E01 The One Where No One Proposes
她真是漂亮
Isn't she beautiful?
瞧瞧她  我第一个孙子
Look at her,my first grandchild.
那本算什么
What about Ben?
本  当然也是
Well,of course,Ben.
我指的是我的第一个孙女
I meant my first granddaughter.
你有想过跟瑞秋之间的可能性吗
Have you thought any more about you and Rachel?
当然
Yeah
事实上我刚才正准备跟她谈
actually I was gonna talk to her
结果你们都涌进来了
when you guys came in the room.
真是太好了
That's so exciting!
即使我们在  你也可以开口啊
You could've done that with us there.
是啊  没错  当然  是啊
Yeah,right.  Sure. Okay.
你能在我们面前自摸
You can touch yourself in front of us,
却不能在我们面前跟瑞秋谈  什么
but you can't talk to Rachel. What?
我何时在你们面前自摸过
When have I ever touched myself in front of you guys?
拜托  之前你在客厅睡着时
Oh,please. Just before,when you were asleep in the lounge.
那些亚美尼亚人都不看电视  反而在看你
That Armenian family was watching you instead of the TV.
这倒提醒了我
That reminds me.
我的游戏机还在贺斯梅先生那里
That Mr. Hazmegian still has my Game Boy.
钱德勒  我可以跟你谈一下吗  当然
Chandler,can I talk to you for a second?  Sure.
兄弟  我刚做了一件很恶劣的事
Dude,I just did something terrible.
是你放的屁吗  我以为是杰克
That was you? I thought it was Jack.
不  那确实是杰克放的
No,no. That was Jack.
瑞秋以为我向她求婚
Rachel thinks I asked her to marry me.
什么  她为什么会那样以为呢
What? Why does she think that?
因为当时看着确实像那么回事儿
Because it kind of looked like I did.
再问一次  什么
Again,what?
好啦  我当时单膝跪在地上
Okay,I was down on one knee
手中拿着戒指...
with the ring in my hand..
是个男人都会偶尔那样练习一下的
As we all are at some point during the day.
那不是我的戒指  是从罗斯的夹克掉出来的
It wasn't my ring. It fell out of Ross' jacket..
当我蹲下去要把它捡起来时
and when I knelt down to pick it up,
瑞秋以为我是在求婚
Rachel thought I was proposing.
罗斯准备了戒指  他要求婚吗
Ross had a ring? And he was gonna propose?
我想是吧  而你抢在他之前先做了
I guess.  And you did it first?
他会痛不欲生的
This is gonna kill him.
你知道他有多爱向人求婚
You know how much he loves to propose.
我知道  我知道  真是太糟糕了
I know. I know. It's awful.
那她说了些什么
Well,what did she say?
她说"我愿意"
She said,"Yes."
罗斯知道吗
Does Ross know?
我的天啊 我该怎么告诉他呢
Oh,my God. What the hell am I gonna tell him?
或许你根本什么都不用告诉他
Maybe you don't have to tell him anything.
我喜欢  甚合我意
I like that. Yeah.
如果你先去跟瑞秋解释清楚
If you clear things up with Rachel,
罗斯就永远不需要知道了
Ross never needs to find out.
但你必须赶快行动
But you have to do it now
别等他发现  然后痛扁你
before he hears about it and kicks your ass.
好吧  我们别扯得太远
All right,let's not get carried away.
我想要个小孩
I want a baby.
亲爱的  我们已经讨论过了
Honey,we've been over this.
我必须要先转过来才行
I need to be facing the other way.
来嘛  来嘛  如果我们再做爱
Come on, come on, If we have sex again,
那我怀孕的机率就会增加一倍
it'll double our chances of getting pregnant.
更衣室现在似乎仍是空的  我好累
I think that closet's still available.  I am so tired.
好啦  但是说好没有前戏哦  没问题
Yeah,okay,but no foreplay.  Deal!
爸  你又放屁
Dad,seriously!
你应该要找医生检查看看了
You know,you really should see someone about that.
知道了
Noted.
我要去找瑞秋谈谈
I wanna go talk to Rachel for a minute.
你自己一个人在这里没问题吧
Are you gonna be okay alone for a bit?
你在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?
我可以目不转睛地看着她到永远
I could stay and look at her forever.
事实上
Actually..
你还好吗
Are you all right?
我想我刚订婚了 天啊  他真求婚了吗
I think I just got engaged.  Oh,my God! He did it?
什么  你知道他要求婚吗
What? Did you know he was gonna ask me?
开什么玩笑  就是我说服他去做的
Are you kidding? I'm,like,the one who talked him into it.
我喜欢自诩为老友团里的玩偶操纵大师
I like to think of myself as the puppet master of the group.
你真认为这是个好主意吗
And you really think this is a good idea?
我才刚说服了他
I just talked him into it.
别连你也要我说服才行
Don't tell me I have to do you too?
操纵师也会累的  拜托  好吧
The puppet master gets tired,people.  Okay.
我不知道  总觉得怪怪的
I don't know. It just doesn't feel right.
为什么  你们简直是天生一对
Why? You two are so meant to be together.
大家都这么认为
Everybody thinks so.
真的吗  即使罗斯也那样认为吗
Really? Even Ross?
特别是罗斯
Especially Ross.
嘿  菲比 我等一下再来
Hey,Phoebe. You know what? I'll come back later.
小病房真是拥挤呢
Kind of a full house here.
我想  我  等一下再来
I guess I'll just.. I'll come back.
他走了  你的未婚夫
There he goes. Your fiance.
我想是吧
I guess so.
不过他会在睡着的时候自摸
Although he does play with himself in his sleep.
我一点也不惊讶
I can't say I'm surprised.
爸  你在做什么
Dad,what are you doing?
有两个人在里面做爱
There are people in there having sex.
不可能是我  我人站在这里
It can't be me. I'm standing right here.
想要偷看吗  不要
Wanna peek?  No!
别这样
Come on.
你知道吗  我讨厌妈不在你身边的时候
You know what? I don't like you without Mom.
走吧
Come on.
我们不偷看吗
We're not peeking?
我还是要偷看
Well,I'm peeking.
我的天啊
Oh,my God!
你好先生  你认识莫妮卡的
Hello,sir. You know Monica.
嘿  可以进来吗  当然可以
Hey,is it okay to come in?  Of course.
乔伊  瞧这戒指  我...
Joey,this ring, I..
真是太美了  我好喜欢
It's beautiful. I love it.
是啊  听着  瑞秋
Yeah. Look, Rach,
有件事我必须要告诉你
there's something I gotta tell you.
你准备好要再试喂母乳了吗
Are you ready to try nursing again?
是啊  嗨  艾玛
Yeah. Hi,Emma.
你觉得她为什么不吸我的奶呢
Why do you think she won't take my breast?
没关系的  婴儿需要一点时间适应
It's all right. It takes babies a while to get it.
不过别担心  她会吸的  好吧
But don't worry,it'll happen.  Okay.
来吧  亲爱的  你可以办得到的
Okay,sweetie,you can do it.
张开嘴巴  然后把它放到嘴里
Just open up and put it in your mouth.
救命啊  上帝
Dear Lord.
我很抱歉  亲爱的  你刚想说什么
I'm sorry,honey,what were you saying?
噢  对  听着  我想...
Yeah,look,I think that..
瞧  她又转开了
Look! She's pulling away again.
会不会是我的乳头对她而言太大了呢
Do you think my nipples are too big for her mouth?
她像是被吓到了
She looks scared.
她看起来是不是像被吓到了呢
Doesn't she look scared?
你知道的  我跟她又不是很熟
You know,I don't really know her.
我们试试看按摩胸部来刺激乳汁分泌
Why don't we try massaging the breast to stimulate the flow?
好的  你在玩我吗
Okay.  Are you kidding me?
真是好沮丧
This is so frustrating.
她为什么不喜欢我的乳房呢
Why doesn't she want my breast?
我不知道  或许她发疯了
I don't know! Maybe she's crazy!
嘿  等一下 嗨
Hey,wait up.  Hi.
恭喜了
Congratulations.
我不想在乔伊面前说出来
I didn't want to say anything in front of Joey.
因为我不清楚他是否已经知道
I didn't know if he knew.
知道什么  我们有了个孩子吗
What? That we had a baby?
我们别太低估他的消息灵通度了
Now let's give him a little credit.
虽然他之前才吃了一个塑料水果
Although he did eat a piece of plastic fruit earlier.
不  我是说你跟瑞秋订婚的事
No,no,that you and Rachel are engaged.
什么  噢  那是秘密吗
What?  Oh,it's a secret?
太棒了  我们很久都没有玩秘密游戏了
Goody. Yes! We haven't done the secret thing in a long time.
菲比  没有什么秘密  好吗
Phoebe,there is no secret,okay?
我都没有求婚
I didn't propose.
你在说谎吗
Are you lying?
是不是又跟上次一样
Is this like that time
你要骗我们你是医生（博士）
you tried to convince us you were a doctor?
我的确是博士
I am a doctor!
算了  我要自己去跟瑞秋谈
You know what? I'm just gonna go and talk to Rachel myself.
好吧  我也去
All right. Well,me too.
要不要叫醒她
Well,should we wake her up?
不  别这样  让她睡
No. No. Come on,let her sleep.
她真的是累坏了  而且真的是订婚了
She's so exhausted.  And so engaged.
我的天  她以为我们订婚了
Oh,my God. She thinks we're engaged!
为什么  她为什么认为我们订婚了呢
Why? Why,why would she think we're engaged?
或许是因为你给了她订婚戒指吗
Perhaps because you gave her an engagement ring?
话说  罗斯  博士应该要是很聪明的
You know,Ross,doctors are supposed to be smart.
我没有给她那个戒指  你没有吗
I didn't give her that ring.  You didn't?
没有   那是谁的戒指呢
No!  So whose ring is it?
是我的
It's mine.
那是订婚戒指吗  是啊
Is it an engagement ring?  Yes.
但是你并没有拿给她  没有
But you didn't give it to her?  No.
但你本来是要求婚的  不是
But you were going to propose?  No!
我可能对这件事没兴趣了
I might be losing interest in this.
听着  我妈给我那个戒指...
Look. Look,my mom gave me that ring..
是因为她要我跟瑞秋求婚
because she wanted me to propose to Rachel.
但是我只想要知道...
But all I wanted to do was see..
她是否愿意再重新开始
if she maybe,kind of wanted to start things up again.
不温不火的恋爱感觉真美好
What beautiful lukewarm sentiment.
听着  我不想要冲动行事
Look. I didn't want to rush into anything.
似乎她也不想要那样
It seemed like she didn't want to either.
但我不明白怎么会变成现在的状况
But I don't understand how any of this happened.
难道是她在我的夹克里找到戒指
What,did she find the ring in my jacket,
然后就认为我要求婚
assume I was gonna propose..
便急着戴上戒指  向大家宣布吗
throw it on and just start telling people?
不  她说你有向她求婚
No,no. She said you actually proposed to her.
我没有  我没有求婚
Well,I didn't! I didn't propose!
除非...
Unless..
我有吗
Did I?
我已经40个小时没睡觉...
I haven't slept in 40 hours and..
那听起来的确像是我会做的事
It does sound like something I would do.
听着  我们不能永远躲在这里
Look,we can't stay in here forever.
我只是不敢相信我爸看到我们在做爱
It's just,I still can't believe that my dad saw us having sex.
我的钢琴独奏会他都一次没去过
He didn't make it to one of my piano recitals,
但他却看到这个
but this he sees!
没关系的  我们都是大人了
This is okay. We're all adults here.
没有什么好丢人的
There's nothing to be ashamed of.
现在  我们把内裤放到口袋里
Now,let's put our underwear in our pockets
然后大胆走出去
and walk out the door.
嗨  爸
Hi,Dad.
我还是可以叫你爸  对吧
I can still call you that,right?
当然  我永远都是你爸
Of course. I'll always be your dad.
我只想让你知道
I just want you to know that
你刚刚目击的行为  并非是为了爽而已
what you witnessed in there,that wasn't for fun.
不爽吗  为什么  为什么你...
It wasn't fun?  Why,why,why would you..?
我只是不想让你认为
Look,I just don't want you to think..
我们像动物一样  随地交配撒欢
that we're animals who do it whenever we want.
我没那样想
Well,I don't think that.
在今天之前  我从未想过你们会做爱
Before today,I never thought of you two having sex at all.
之前的想法要单纯的多
It was a simpler time.
事实是  爸  我们正在努力
The truth is,Dad,we're trying.
什么  是啊  我们正在努力弄大肚子
What?  Yeah,we're trying to get pregnant.
我的天啊  真是太好了
Oh,my God,this is so exciting.
快进去继续"努力"  我来看门
Well,get back in there! I'll guard the door!
没关系  爸  我们可以等会儿再说
That's okay,Dad,we can wait until later.
我可不同意 你不是正在排卵吗
I don't think so. Aren't you ovulating?
爸
Daddy!
你要把握时机  小公主
You gotta get at it,princess.
当年你妈跟我试着要怀你的时候
When your mother and I were trying to conceive you..
只要她在排卵  我们就做
whenever she was ovulating,bam,we did it!
所以我现在臀部都落下了病根
That's how I got my bad hip.
真好笑   你们的对话简直
That's funny. This conversation's
让我的脑袋像被子弹打穿一样
how I got the bullet hole in my head.
有一次我把膝盖架到洗手台上
This one time I had my knee on the sink,
而你妈...
and your mother, she was..
我想我们不需要知道
I don't think we need to hear
你跟我妈的特殊体位
the specific positions you and Mom had.
没错  现在的问题是你们的体位
You're right. This is about your positions.
我刚看到你们在更衣室里
Now,what I saw in the closet
采用的并非是最佳受孕体位
is not the optimum position..for conceiving a child.
虽然那感觉可能会很爽
Although it might feel good.
我现在感觉非常不爽
I don't feel good right now.
但是快感是很重要的
But pleasure is important,
而且如果女人达到高潮  受孕会更容易
and it helps if the woman has an orgasm.
你能完成任务吗  猛男
You up to the task,sailor?
我需要告诉你一件事
Oh,I need to tell you something.
现在正是时候
Well,now's a good time.
我正要去把我的耳朵切掉
I'm on my way to have my ears cut off.
乔伊要我嫁给他
Joey asked me to marry him.
什么  乔伊向我求婚
What?  Joey proposed to me.
他疯了吗  你才刚生下罗斯的孩子
Is he crazy? You just had Ross' baby!
我答应了
Well,I said yes.
什么  你疯了吗
What,are you crazy?
你才刚生下罗斯的孩子
You just had Ross' baby!
那太不合适了  不  比那更恶劣
It's so inappropriate. No,it is worse than that.
简直是有违道德  简直
It is wrong. It's...
钻戒比我的大多了
It is bigger than mine!
我知道
I know.
《我们的日子》 真是太感谢电视了
Days of our Lives,thank you very much.
你不能嫁给他  为什么不能
You can't marry him.  Why not?
我不想要一个人苦撑
Come on,I don't want to do this alone,
而且他是个好人
and he's such a sweet guy.
而且他很爱我
And he loves me so much.
那你爱他吗
Well,do you love him?
当然
Sure.
当然  是啊  我是说  随便啦
Sure?  Yeah,I mean,whatever.
亲爱的  问题是
Honey,the question is..
你是真的想嫁给乔伊吗
do you really want to marry Joey?
不
No.
不  我不想
No,I don't.
你能行行好帮我去告诉他吗
Could you be a dear and go tell him?
你还没告诉瑞秋你当时不是在求婚吗
You still haven't told Rachel you weren't proposing?
没  她戴上了戒指
No. She had the ring on..
她看起来很兴奋  然后她露出胸部
she seemed so excited,and then she took her breast out.
乔伊  你得告诉她真相
Joey,you have to tell her what's going on.
胸部看起来怎样
And what did it look like?
我没看到
I didn't look at it.
大部分都被那死小孩的头给挡住了
The stupid baby's head was blocking most of it.
马上去跟瑞秋说  别等罗斯发现
Go and tell Rachel right now,before Ross finds out.
听着  事情没那么简单
Look,it's not that easy.
她说她想要嫁给我
She said she wanted to marry me.
我不想伤害她
I don't want to hurt her.
好啦  反正  就温和地告诉她
Okay,look,just do it gently.
你说的没错  很有道理
You're right. You're right.
我得在罗斯知道之前赶快说清楚
I'll go tell her now before Ross finds out,
而且我会很温和的
and I'll be gentle.
我办得到的  我是个温和的人
I can do that. I am a gentle person.
对了  有两个人在里面胡搞
By the way,two people screwing in there
你可以饱饱眼福
if you want to check that out.
我听说订婚的事了
Listen,I heard about the engagement.
惊讶吧
Surprised?
而且很困惑
And confused.
瑞秋  亲爱的
Rach,sweetie..
我没有向你求婚
I didn't propose to you.
我知道
I know.
我觉得你并不知道
I don't think you do.
你没有向我求婚
You didn't propose to me.
是乔伊向我求婚
Joey did.
可怜的宝贝  你累坏了
Poor baby,you're so tired.
瑞秋  我没有向你求婚
Rach,I didn't propose to you.
乔伊没有向你求婚
Joey didn't propose to you.
钱德勒也没有向你求婚
And Chandler didn't propose to you.
你没有向我求婚
You didn't propose to me.
钱德勒没有向我求婚
Chandler didn't propose to me.
但是乔伊有
But Joey did.
乔伊向你求婚
Joey proposed to you?
我可以等一下再来  等等  等等
I can come back.  Wait. Wait. Wait.
乔伊  你有向她求婚吗  没有
Joey,did you propose to her?  No.
你有  事实上  严格说来  我没有
Yes,you did.  Actually,technically,I didn't.
那你为什么给我戒指呢  等一下
Well,then,why did you give me a ring?  Wait.
戒指是你给她的?
You gave her the ring?
没有  而且我也没向她求婚
No,and I did not ask her to marry me.
有  你有  不  我没有
Yes,you did.  No,I didn't.
你有  我没有
你有  别再说你没有了
Yes,you did,and don't you say you didn't!
他当时就在床前
He was right there.
单膝跪地  然后向我求婚
He got down on one knee and he proposed.
你单膝跪地  是啊  形象全毁
You were down on one knee?  Yeah,that looks bad.
但是我并没有求婚
But  I didn't, I didn't propose.
那到底是怎么回事
Then what did happen?
是啊  到底是怎么回事
Yeah,what did happen?
是这样的  当时戒指掉到了地上
Okay,the ring fell on the floor,
然后我蹲下去捡
and I went down to pick it up..
然后你就以为我是在求婚
and you thought I was proposing.
但是你嘴里说着"嫁给我好吗"
Yeah,but you said,"Will you marry me?"
不  我没说  有  你有
No,I didn't.  Yes,you did.
不  我没有
No,I didn't.
有  你有  噢  天啊  你并没有
Yes,you did. Oh,my God,you didn't.
你为什么不早点说呢
Why didn't you tell me that before?
我也想啊  但是一直有人进来打断
Well,I tried.. but people kept coming in,
然后你又露出胸部
and then you took your breast out.
你看到她的胸部了
You saw her breast?
我待会再告诉你  冷静点
I'll tell you about it later. Be cool.
那乔伊你拿个戒指搞什么
Then Joey, what the hell were you doing with an engagement ring?
那不是我的戒指  是罗斯的
It wasn't my ring! It's Ross' ring.
正因此我才觉得好内疚  瑞秋
That's why I felt so bad, Rach,
因为他本来是打算求婚的
because he was gonna propose.
什么
What?!
你本来要向我求婚
You were gonna propose to me?
没有
No.
噢  这下尴尬了
Well,this is awkward.
但是我本来是要问你
But I was going to see if,you know,
是否愿意跟我重新开始
maybe you wanted to start dating again.
但  我是说  仅此而已  瑞秋
But that,I mean,that was all,Rach.
老兄  勇敢点吧  我都求婚了
Dude,step up. I proposed.
不  你没有
No,you didn't.
没错  发生太多事了
That's right. There's a lot going on here,
我之前一定是吃了什么腐坏的水果
and I think I ate some bad fruit earlier.
嘿  她刚醒来  而且饿了
Hey,she just woke up. She's hungry.
我们再来试试看吧
Why don't we give this another try?
我不敢相信你竟然告诉她我要求婚
I can't believe you told her I was gonna propose.
我不敢相信你竟然不打算求婚
I can't believe you're not gonna propose.
嘿  我才不要头脑发热一时冲动呢
Hey,I am not gonna rush into anything.
是啊  老兄  我完全理解
Yeah,dude,I totally understand.
在跟一个女人有了小孩之后
Usually after I have a baby with a woman,
才想着要放慢脚步
I like to slow things down!
噢  天啊   怎么了
Oh,my God!  What?
她在吸了  她在吸奶了  瞧啊
She's doing it! She's breastfeeding! Look.
真是太美了
It's beautiful.
我等一下再回来抱她  好的
I'll come back for her later. OK
谢谢你
Thank you.
哇  感觉好怪
Wow,this feels weird.
怎么  是好的那种吗
What,good weird?
简直爽透了
Wonderful weird.
那个  我也先走了
You know what,you guys? I'm gonna go too.
我很抱歉  我搞出来的闹剧
And I'm sorry about everything.
亲爱的  别担心  是我的错
Honey,don't worry,it was my mistake.
不  瑞秋  我应该早点告诉你的
No,Rach,I should've told you sooner.
只不过...
It's just that..
天啊  那小孩吸得真起劲儿
Man,that kid is going to town!
她真是完美
She's perfect.
我们真幸运
We're so lucky.
我们确实很幸运
We really are.
听着  我知道那不是求婚
Look,I know it's not a proposal,
我也不知道你的意思如何
and I don't know where you are..
但是有了艾玛之后  我...
but with everything that's been going on and with Emma,I'm..
我一直感到...  是的  我懂
I've been feeling..  Yeah,I know.
我也感到...
I've been feeling..
是吗  是啊
Yeah?  Yeah.
好的  那么  那...
Okay,well,that..
哇  好的  那么...
Wow,okay,well..
那么或许我们可以再考虑在一起
Then maybe at least we can talk about us again?
是啊  或许吧
Yeah. Maybe.
那  很好  好的
Well,good. Okay.
我想着  如果我们  如果...
I kind of think,you know,if we,if..
你手上戴着戒指
You're wearing the ring.
你说什么
What's that?
你告诉菲比你订婚了
And you told Phoebe you were engaged.
不好意思  你说什么
I'm sorry,what?
当你以为乔伊是在求婚
When you thought Joey proposed..
你有答应吗
did you say yes?
孩子们  我找了一下医生
Kids,I spoke to a doctor
拿了些受孕教育手册
and picked up these pamphlets on how to get pregnant.
嗨  爸  嗨
Hey,Dad.  Hi.
很抱歉再次打扰你们
Sorry to bother you again,
但是能不能把我的受孕手册传出来呢
but could you pass my pamphlets back?
谢谢
Thank you.